<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<!DOCTYPE MudletPackage>
<MudletPackage version="1.001">
	<TriggerPackage />
	<TimerPackage />
	<AliasPackage />
	<ActionPackage />
	<ScriptPackage>
		<ScriptGroup isActive="yes" isFolder="yes">
			<name>Script_Help</name>
			<packageName></packageName>
			<script>--[[
Likely the basic answers you want on triggers are at:
  https://wiki.mudlet.org/w/Manual:Scripting
  
In short scripts are a collection of code that either runs on startup or is called
by other mudlet features like triggers or aliases
The way Parthia is written, we create our code the the scripts section as functions.
After that we call them with the mudlet feature needed to run the function at the correct time.
This allows us to use one function in many situations.
That does not mean you need to write that way. Write Your_Code they way that is best for you.

Any code written in the Your_Scripts folder will never be changed by Pathia updates.
We highly recommend backing up all the Your_ files in your `The Eternal City` mudlet profile.
We have made an aliase to easy open the folder these files are in.
To run it type `tecclient Your_Files`
Also you will see that aliase in Your_Aliases folder.

Parthia is intended to be a community project.
As we wrote code we made certain to comment nearly every line.
There will be many examples to reference scripts in TEC_Client_Scripts.
Further more in TEC_Client_Cripts/TECFunctions there are many functions that you may be able 
to use yourself. As time goes on the comments preceding each script will likely become more detailed.

We are happy to answer questions.
Parthia's discord server is: https://discord.gg/QGztVx
Our github page is: https://github.com/TheEternalCitizens/mudlet-integration

Another wonderful source of answers and knowledge is:
Mudlet's discord server: https://discord.gg/FfkEx7
mudlet manual: https://wiki.mudlet.org/w/Manual:Contents
mudlet function reference: https://wiki.mudlet.org/w/Manual:Lua_Functions
  ^This is not a complete list but it is a wonderful start^
  
Good lua references:
https://www.lua.org/pil/contents.html
https://docs.coronalabs.com/api/index.html --Good for if you already know the basics.

As you write code you can share it at the parthia discord server on the player-scripts channel.
]]--</script>
			<eventHandlerList />
		</ScriptGroup>
	</ScriptPackage>
	<KeyPackage />
	<HelpPackage>
		<helpURL></helpURL>
	</HelpPackage>
</MudletPackage>
